Guide to the Cornell University News Service records, [ca. 1920s-2000s].
Cornell University News Service records
- Series VI. Cornell University News Services records, 1920s-2000s
  - Press Releases, News Clippings, Distribution Lists, Administrative Files, Subject Files
    - Alpha Subject File, 1990s-2000s
      - Law School (Box 4-3-15 - 142)
        - Law School Releases, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 27)
        - Law School Releases, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 28)
        - Law School Releases, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 29)
        - Law School Releases, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 30)
        - Law School Releases, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 31)
        - Law School Releases, 1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 32)
        - Law School Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 33)
      - Lectures (Box 4-3-15 - 142)
        - Lectures - Bartels Lectures, 1990-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 34)
        - Lectures - Becker Lectures, 1988-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 35)
        - Lectures - Belnick Lectures, 2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 36)
        - Lectures - Bethe Lectures, 1990-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 37)
        - Lectures - Kaplan Lectures, 2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 38)
        - Lectures - Durland Lectures, 1993-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 39)
        - Lectures - Einaudi Lectures, 1988-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 40)
        - Lectures - Flemmie Kittrell Lectures, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 41)
        - Lectures - Hatfield Lectures, 1991-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 42)
        - Lectures - Sumner Lectures, 1993-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 43)
        - Lectures - Messenger Lectures, 1990-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 44)
        - Lectures - Olin Lectures, 1990-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 45)
        - Lectures - Preston H. Thomas Memorial Lectures, 1990-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 46)
        - Lectures - Raymond G. Thorpe Lectures, 1993-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 47)
        - Lectures - Robert S. Stevens Lectures, 1993-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 48)
        - Lectures - Kops Fellowship Lectures, 1994-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 142, Folder 49)
        - Lectures - Walter LaFeber Joel Silbey Fund Lectures, 1997-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 1)
        - Lectures - Thomas Gold Lecture, 1993-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 2)
        - Lectures - University Lectures News Releases, 1995-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 3)
        - Lectures - Johnson Memorial Lectures, 2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 4)
        - Lectures - Julian C. Smith Lectures, 1994-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 5)
        - Lectures - University Lectures Releases, 2000-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 6)
        - Lectures - Iscol Lecture, 2000-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 7)
        - Lectures - University Lectures Release, 1993-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 8)
        - Lectures -University Lectures Releases, 1990-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 9)
        - Lectures - University Lectures Clips, 1993-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 10)
        - Lectures - Lectures Miscellaneous, 1964-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 11)
      - Legal Information Institute(LII), 2001-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 12)
      - Field of Lesbian, Bisexual and Gay Studies, 1992-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 13)
      - Field of Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender Resource Office, 1994-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 14)
      - University Libraries Digital Library, 2001-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 15)
      - Libraries Echols Collection, 1994-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 16)
      - Engineering Library (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 17)
      - University Library, Internet First University Press, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 18)
      - Kroch Library Clips, 1992-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 19)
      - Kroch Library Releases, 1992-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 20)
      - Mann Library Releases, 1999-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 21)
      - Mann Library Clips, 1992-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 22)
      - Libraries: Manuscripts and Archives, 1991-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 23)
      - Libraries: Manuscripts and Archives Mariposa Foundation, 1988-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 24)
      - Libraries: Olin Library, 1990s (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 25)
      - Libraries: Uris Library, 1986-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 26)
      - Cornell Library Miscellaneous (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 27)
      - "Epoch" and Cornell Libraries, 1980s (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 28)
      - Libraries Releases, 1997-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 29)
      - Libraries Releases, 1995-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 30)
      - Libraries: Donated Collections (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 31)
      - Libraries Clips, 1991-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 143, Folder 32)
      - Mann Library Releases, Prior to 1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 1)
      - Clips for Donating Collections, 1990s (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 2)
      - Abigail Adams Papers, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 3)
      - Joan Jacobs Brumberg Papers, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 4)
      - Events-Johnson Family Papers (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 5)
      - Abigail Adams and Joan Jacobs Brumberg Papers (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 6)
      - Mars Rover Cornell, 2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 7)
      - Mars Rover Landing (videos), 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 8)
      - Mars Rover Landing (clips), 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 9)
      - Mars Rover Landing, 2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 10)
      - Mars Landing, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 11)
      - Mars Landing, February 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 12)
      - Mars Landing, March 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 13)
      - Mars Landing, April 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 14)
      - Mars Landing, May 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 15)
      - Media Services Resource Center, 1990-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 16)
      - Minority Education Affairs Office of COSEP Release, 1982-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 17)
      - Minority Education Affairs Office of COSEP Clips, 1982-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 18)
      - Scenic Information, 1995-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 19)
      - General Information, 1996-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous Information, 1996-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 21)
      - National Association of College and University Business Officers NACUBO, 21982-1990004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 22)
      - Section of Neurobiology and Behavior Releases, 1976-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 23)
      - Section of Neurobiology and Behavior Clips, 1986-2005 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 24)
      - New York Compact, 2001-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 25)
      - News Releases, 2001-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 26)
      - News Releases, 1999-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 144, Folder 27)
      - News Releases, 1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 1)
      - News Releases, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 2)
      - Northeast Regional Climate Center Releases, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 3)
      - Northeast Regional Climate Center Releases, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 4)
      - Northeast Regional Climate Center Releases, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 5)
      - Northeast Regional Climate Center Releases, 1992-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 6)
      - Northeast Regional Climate Center Clips, 1997-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 7)
      - Northeast Regional Climate Center Clips, 1993-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 7)
      - Office of Ombudsman, 1969-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 8)
      - Cornell Orchards, 1996-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 9)
      - Cornell Orchard Facilities and Buildings, 1988-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 10)
      - Patents and Technology Marketing, 1975-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 11)
      - Peace Corps, 1997-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 12)
      - Peace Studies Program, 1973-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 13)
      - James A. Perkins Prize, 1995-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 14)
      - Planning, Design and Construction, 1997-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 15)
      - Cornell Plantations Releases, 2000-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 16)
      - Cornell Plantations Releases, 1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 17)
      - Cornell Plantations Releases, 1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 18)
      - Cornell Plantations Releases, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 19)
      - Cornell Plantations Releases, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 20)
      - Cornell Plantations Releases, 1994-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 21)
      - Cornell Plantations Releases, 1990-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 22)
      - Cornell Plantations Clips, 1994-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 23)
      - Laboratory for Plasma Studies, 1973-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 24)
      - Cornell Police Department Clips, 1995-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 145, Folder 25)
      - Cornell Police Department Releases, 2001-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 1)
      - Cornell Police Department Releases, 1996-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 2)
      - Cornell Police Department Releases, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 3)
      - Cornell Police Department Releases, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 4)
      - Cornell Police Department Releases, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 5)
      - Cornell Police Department Releases, 1990-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 6)
      - Cornell Police Department - Blue Light Escort Service, 1982-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 7)
      - Cornell Police Department Releases, 2001-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 8)
      - Policies: Grievance Procedure, 1972-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 9)
      - Policies: Holiday Policy, 1973-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 10)
      - Policies: Smoking Policy, 1988-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 11)
      - Policies Misc., 1993-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 12)
      - Presidential Research Scholars Program, 2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 13)
      - Women: Advisory Committee on the Status of Women Releases, 1980-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 14)
      - Women: Advisory Committee on the Status of Women Clips, 1981-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 15)
      - Women: Advisory Committee on the Status of Women, 1974-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 16)
      - Presidential Search Committee, 1994-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 17)
      - Professors-at-large A.D. White Releases, 2001-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 18)
      - Professors-at-large A.D. White Releases, 1998-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 19)
      - Professors-at-large A.D. White Releases, 1996-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 20)
      - Professors-at-large A.D. White Releases, 1994-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 21)
      - Professors-at-large A.D. White Releases, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 22)
      - Professors-at-large A.D. White Releases, 1990-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 23)
      - Professors-at-large A.D. White Clips, 1994-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 24)
      - FAQs About Cynthia McKinney as a Frank H.T. Rhodes Class of '56 University Professor, 2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 25)
      - A.D. White Professor at Large, General Information, 1994-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 26)
      - Professorships: Don and Margi Berens Professor of Entrepreneurship, 1982-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 27)
      - Professorships: Kenneth and Marjorie Blanchard Professor of Human Resource Manag., 1986-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 28)
      - J. Thomas Clark Chair, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 29)
      - Professorships: Newton C. Farr Professor of Amer. History and Culture, 1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 30)
      - Professorships: Anne Evans Gibbons Professorship, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 31)
      - Professorship: Jacob Gould Schurman Professor of Biology, 1976-1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 32)
      - Ilda and Charles Lee Professorship of Engineering, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 33)
      - Professorship: Newman Professorship in American Civilization, 1986-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 34)
      - Professorships: Nicholas H. Noyes Professor of Manufacturing, 1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 35)
      - Professorships: Frank H.T. Rhodes Class of '56, 2002-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 36)
      - Professorships: HU Shih Chair in Chinese Studies, 1991-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 37)
      - Professorships: Tisch Professorship, 2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 38)
      - Assorted Releases and Clippings, 1973-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 39)
      - MSA - Accreditation, 1992-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 40)
      - Provost's Office, 1993-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 41)
      - Cornell Public Service Center Releases, 1994-2005 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 42)
      - Cornell Public Service Center, 1996-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 43)
      - Cornell Public Service Center General Info, 1994-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 44)
      - Cornell Public Service Center - Civic Fellowship Program, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 45)
      - Cornell Public Service center Community Partnership Fund, 1999-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 46)
      - Cornell Public Service Center, Into the Streets, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 47)
      - Cornell Public Service Center Robinson-Appel Humanitarian Award, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 48)
      - Cornell Public Service Center Releases, 2000-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 49)
      - Office of Purchasing Services, 1972-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 50)
      - Real Estate, 1978-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 51)
      - Research and Advanced Studies, 1991-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 146, Folder 52)
      - Office of Research and Advanced Studies, 1977-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 1)
      - Risk Management and Insurance, 2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 2)
      - ROTC Releases, 1963-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 3)
      - ROTC Clips, 1951-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 4)
      - Sea Grant Program, 1971-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 5)
      - Shoals Marine Laboratory, 1973-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 6)
      - Sponsored Programs Releases, 1971-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 7)
      - Sponsored Programs Clips, 1980-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 8)
      - State University of New York (SUNY), 1994-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 9)
      - Statler Hotel, 1989-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 10)
      - Statuatory Colleges Releases, 1990-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 11)
      - Statuatory Colleges Clips, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 12)
      - Statuatory Colleges Clips, 1993-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 13)
      - Statuatory Colleges Clips, 1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 14)
      - Statuatory Colleges Clips, 1990-1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 15)
      - Statuatory Colleges Clips, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 16)
      - Statuatory Colleges Releases, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 17)
      - Statuatory Colleges Layoff, 1975-1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 18)
      - Issues/Events, Straight Takeover - 20th Anniversary (Box 4-3-15 - 147, Folder 19)
      - Students
        - Students, Misc., Late 1990s-2000s (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 1)
        - Students Clips, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 2)
        - Students Clips, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 3)
        - Students Clips, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 4)
        - Students Clips, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 5)
        - Students Clips, 1992-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 6)
        - Students Releases, 1993-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 7)
        - Students Profiles, 1987-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 8)
        - Students Publications, 1984-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 9)
        - Students Publications - Cornell Daily Sun, 1950-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 10)
        - Students Articles, 1991-2000s (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 11)
        - Students, Student Agencies, 1981-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 12)
        - Students Activities Clips, 1995-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 13)
        - Students Activities Clips, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 14)
        - Students Misc., 2000s (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 15)
        - Students Activities Clips, 2000-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 16)
        - Students Activities Clips, 1998-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 17)
        - Students Crime/Arrests, 1983-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 18)
        - Students Awards, 1995-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 19)
        - Students Awards Releases, 1994-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 20)
        - Students Awards Clips, 1993-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 21)
        - Students Awards Clips, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 22)
        - Students Misc. Photographs of Winners, 1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 23)
        - Students - Awards, Merrill Presidential Releases - Digital Photo CD, 2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 24)
        - Students - Awards, Merrill Presidential Clips, 1992-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 25)
        - Students - Awards, Rhodes Scholarships, 1984-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 26)
        - Students Census, 2001-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 27)
        - Students Chinese Students and Scholars Association, 2000-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 28)
        - Students Cornell Olympics, 2002-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 29)
        - Events - Day Hall Occupation, November 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 148, Folder 30)
        - Students Housing, 1994-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 1)
        - Students, President Rawlings Campus Housing Plan, September 8, 1997 (Press Release) (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 2)
        - Students Housing, 2002-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 3)
        - Students Housing North Campus, 2001-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 4)
        - West Campus Housing, 2003-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 5)
        - West Campus Initiative, 2003-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 6)
        - Students Incoming, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 7)
        - Students - International Students Programming Board, 1996-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 8)
        - Students Issues Latino Issues, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 9)
        - Students Issues and Events Demonstrations, 1991-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 10)
        - Students Kyoto Now!, 2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 11)
        - Students - Student Life Union, 1992-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 12)
        - Students Meningitis, 2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 13)
        - Students Mock Election, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 14)
        - Students New Freshman Reading Project, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 15)
        - Students Organizations, 1983-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 16)
        - Students Orientation, 1972-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 17)
        - Students Solar Decathalon Team, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 18)
        - Students - Student and Academic Services, 1991-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 19)
        - Students - Student Assembly, 2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 20)
        - Students Young Israel, 1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 21)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 1991-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 22)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 1997-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 23)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 24)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 19199596 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 25)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 26)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 27)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 28)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 29)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Clips, 1990-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 30)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Superquest, 1989-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 31)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering SPI -IBM, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 32)
      - Center for Theory and Simulation in Science and Engineering Misc. (Box 4-3-15 - 149, Folder 33)
      - Transportation Services Clips, 1975-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 1)
      - Transportation Services Parking Garage, 1986-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 2)
      - Transportation Services Releases, 2000-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 3)
      - Transportation and Mail Services TCAT - Death of Michelle Evans, 2000-2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 4)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 2002-2005 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 5)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1999-2001 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 6)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 7)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 8)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 9)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 10)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 11)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 12)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1992 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 13)
      - Board of Trustees: Presidential Search Committee, 2002 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 14)
      - Board of Trustees: Presidential Councillors, 1966-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 15)
      - Board of Trustees, 1992-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 16)
      - Board of Trustees News Clippings, 1983-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 17)
      - Board of Trustees Releases, 1990s (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 18)
      - United Way, 1993-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 19)
      - University Human Resource Services Releases, 1993-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 20)
      - University Human Resource Services Clips, 1996-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 21)
      - University Human Resource Services Benefits Services, 1994-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 22)
      - University Human Resource Services Cornell Recruitment Partnership, 2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 23)
      - University Human Resource Services Labor Relations, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 24)
      - University Human Resource Services Labor Relations: Building Trades Council, 1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 25)
      - University Human Resource Services Labor Relations:Security Employees Union, 1982-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 26)
      - University Human Resource Services United Auto Workers, 1994-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 27)
      - University Human Resource Services United Auto Workers, Prior to 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 28)
      - University Human Resource Services University Summer Day Camp, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 29)
      - University Human Resource Services Wellness Program, 1994-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 30)
      - University Human Resource Services Misc., 1980-1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 31)
      - Community Relations Releases, 2000-2005 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 32)
      - Community Relations Releases, 1998-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 33)
      - Community Relations Releases, 1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 34)
      - Community Relations Releases, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 35)
      - Community Relations Releases, 1993-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 36)
      - Community Relations Clips, 2000-2004 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 37)
      - Community Relations Clips, 1997-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 38)
      - Community Relations Clips, 1995-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 39)
      - Community Relations Clips, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 40)
      - Community Relations Collegetown, 1994-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 41)
      - Town-Gown Clips and Releases, 1995-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 42)
      - Signing of City/CU Memorandum of Understanding, 1995-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 150, Folder 43)
      - University Relations Releases, 1988-2003 (Box 4-3-15 - 151, Folder 1)
      - University Relations Communication Strategies, 1994-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 151, Folder 2)